<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CHIRST APP</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="planets_array">
        <item>Placement</item>
        <item>Job</item>
        <item>Both</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="placemnt">Placemnt</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="placement">placement</string>

    <string name="article_title">Article By Joswin Dsouza Reg No: 2047218</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">About Us</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Admission is Live! Visit the college site above</string>
    <string name="article_text">CHRIST (Deemed to be University) was born out of the educational vision of <i>St Kuriakose Elias Chavara</i>, an educationalist and social reformer of the nineteenth century in South India. He founded the first Catholic indigenous congregation, Carmelites of Mary Immaculate (CMI), in 1831 which administers CHRIST (Deemed to be University).
        For more information, see the Christ website https://christuniversity.in
\n\n
<b>History:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>Established in 1969</i></b>  as Christ College, it undertook path-breaking initiatives in Indian higher education with the introduction of innovative and modern curricula, insistence on academic discipline, imparting of Holistic Education and adoption of global higher education practices with the support of creative and dedicated staff. The University Grants Commission (UGC) of India conferred Autonomy to Christ College in 2004 and identified it as an Institution with Potential for Excellence in 2006. In 2008 under Section 3 of the UGC Act, 1956, the Ministry of Human Resource Development of the Government of India, declared the institution a Deemed to be University, in the name and style of Christ University. One of the first institutions in India to be accredited in 1998 by the NAAC, and subsequently in 2004 and 2016, CHRIST (Deemed to be University) has the top grade A in the 4-point scale.
\n\n
<b><i>The multi-disciplinary University</i></b> which focuses on teaching research and service offers Bachelor, Master and Doctoral programmes in humanities, social sciences, science, commerce, management, engineering, education, and law to over 27000 students. The University offers its programmes at three campuses in Bangalore in Karnataka; Pune Lavasa in Maharashtra and Delhi NCR. The campus is a living example of harmonious multiculturalism with students from all the states and union territories and around 60 different countries. CHRIST (Deemed to be University) publishes six peer-reviewed research journals and has published more than 300 books in Kannada and English. A promoter of sports, music and literary activities, it is a nurturing ground for creative excellence.
\n\n
<b><i>Vision Misson</i></b> CHRIST (Deemed to be University), a premier educational institution, is an academic fraternity of individuals dedicated to the motto of EXCELLENCE AND SERVICE.

We strive to reach out to the star of perfection through an earnest academic pursuit for excellence, and our efforts blossom into service through our creative and empathetic involvement in the society to transform it.

Education prepares one to face the challenges of life by bringing out the best in him or her. If this is well accepted, education should be relevant to the needs of the time and address the problems of the day. Being inspired by Blessed Kuriakose Elias Chavara, the founder of Carmelites of Mary Immaculate and the pioneer in innovative education, CHRIST (Deemed to be University) was proactive to define and redefine its mission and strategies reading the signs of the time.
\n\n
<b><i>Core Value</i></b> The values which guide us at CHRIST (Deemed to be University) are:

Faith in God
Moral Uprightness
Love of Fellow Beings
Social Responsibility
Pursuit of Excellence
\n\n
<b><i>Founder</i></b> CHRIST (Deemed to be University) was born out of the educational vision of St Kuriakose Elias Chavara (1805-1871), an educationalist and a social reformer of the nineteenth century South India. In his childhood, Kuriakose attended the village school where he studied language and elementary sciences. He entered the seminary in 1818 and was ordained a priest in 1829. St Chavara founded the congregation of Carmelites of Mary Immaculate (CMI), in 1831 with a vision to serve the marginalized and underprivileged.
\n\n
</string>
    <string name="my_image_desc">My Image Desc</string>
    <string name="change_background">Change Background</string>
    <string name="admission_status">Admission Status</string>
    <string name="Placement">Placement</string>
    <string name="christ_app">CHRIST APP</string>
</resources>